(Leonard:)Doesn't seem like it. She got Sheldon
to go to a psychic with her.
(Amy:)A psychic? He considers them
not just mumbo jumbo,
(Amy:)but extra-jumbo mumbo jumbo.
(Leonard:)Well, Penny can be very persuasive.
(Leonard:)She's gotten me to do a lot
of things I wouldn't normally do.
(Amy:)-Because she has sex with you.
-Yeah, she does.
(Amy:)Can I confess something?
(Amy:)Once in a while,
I get a little jealous
(Amy:)of how close Penny
and Sheldon are.
(Howard:)-Really?
-I mean, not in a romantic way.
(Amy:)It's just, she really has some
sort of connection with him.
(Leonard:)Well... Well, they've known
each other a long time,
(Leonard:)and Penny grew up around horses,
(Leonard:)so she knows how to approach him
without making him skittish.
(Amy:)Don't get me wrong.
I'm glad they're friends.
(Amy:)I just wish he'd be that
comfortable around me already.
(Leonard:)Well, it took him a long time
to get comfortable around me, too.
(Amy:)Really? What did you do?
(Leonard:)Something terrible in a former life?
I don't know.
(Bernadette:)I gotta go.
Penny ratted me out.